It's been a long time, Kizuna.
Mother...
What's going on?
Why is Dr. Nayuta here?
Let's leave this to Kizuna-kun.
Dr. Nayuta...
Seven years and twenty-one days, huh?
You've grown up while I wasn't around.
What happened, Mom?
What are you doing here,
on a Batlantis battleship?
Part of my field work.
I needed to go to the Batlantis Empire
for my research.
Research?
You are not needed anymore.
There's so much I want to ask you.
But first, come back to Ataraxia.
We can talk then.
I can't.
My research isn't finished yet.
What the hell do you mean, "research"?!
That voice... Reiri, am I right?
Why are you in bed with the enemy?
What are you plotting?
Reiri, you can't understand
the meaning of my actions?
Hell no!
You really are stupid.
Oh, but no need to worry about it.
They say the stupider your child,
the more lovable they are.
And most people are stupid.
Kizuna!
Bring her back!
Mom!
A hologram?
Sorry,
but that's all for today.
I just came to deliver a message to you.
If you want to see me, come to Tokyo.
I'm sure you'll find something interesting.
To Tokyo?
And...
Bye, Kizuna.
I'll see you in Tokyo.
Wait!
I want you to do something
about everybody's core!
How can the cores be removed?
How can I save them all?
Tell me!
Mom!
Um, we're done.
So leave.
Well, I'm not done!
Give me back my mom!
Kicking us out all of a sudden? How rude!
Kizuna!
Are you okay?
What was that?
Huh?
How do you like that?
I am the great Ragres,
and this is my Magitech armor, Demon!
It's so huge!
Is that really a Heart Hybrid Gear?
Now come get some!
Take that! And that!
W-Wait!
Mom!
Why?
Episode 10
Eve of the Decisive Battle -Install-
Why do the proud royal guards
have to flee from the enemy?
Did you show pity on them
because they're fellow Lemurians?
That was our chance to catch Zeros!
I'm afraid our only goal there
was to meet them.
Capturing Zeros wasn't part of the plan.
Zelshione-sama w-was aware of this...
Please wait a moment.
She told us to do everything
Nayuta-sama said.
But Nayuta-sama...
Now that they know we'll be waiting for them,
will they really come to Tokyo?
They'll come, Varde.
Because I set things up so they would.
What?
The plan to retake Tokyo
was all a setup by Mom?
What are you saying, Sis?
Yeah.
Now I'm sure of it.
Kizuna, we found out about
your Eros unit's unique ability,
restoring Hybrid Counts with Heart Hybrids,
via data sent from an anonymous source.
Someone sent it to us...
You don't mean...
The impetus for the operation to retake Tokyo
was the data we acquired that
allowed us to reseal Entrances.
That data was also submitted by
an unknown party from Guam.
And you're saying that was Dr. Nayuta?
Only a genius scientist like Nayuta Hida
would be capable of putting
together such perfect data.
Then what do we do now, Sis?
We have to go.
No matter what's waiting for us.
Even if it's a trap set by a witch.
That's what I like to hear.
Aine?
Don't make weird noises.
I'll just obey orders if I have to, is all.
Wait, Aine-san!
Oh, dear. It's like
she's back to the old Aine.
Wait, Kizuna.
There's something else I need to tell you.
What?
A new Amaterasu candidate?
We need talented people
to take back Tokyo.
But that means
installing a Heart Hybrid Gear core, right?
In other words...
I'm aware.
I'm no better than that woman.
But we can't lose this fight,
if we want this war to end someday.
Sis...
This is the list of candidates.
Th-This is...
Okay, see you tomorrow, Sylvia-chan!
Bye-bye, Sylvia!
Bye!
Okay, what should I cook today?
Sylvia!
Captain?
You want me to be
a Heart Hybrid Gear pilot?
Y-Yeah...
You've got the grades and aptitude for it.
Then I can be a part of
Amaterasu, too, can't I?
No, you should think about it
more before you decide.
This is an important decision for you.
Nobody will complain if you refuse.
Captain?
I won't force you.
If you don't want to, you don't have to.
You don't have to fight.
Why are you saying that?
I'm saying you don't have to
force yourself to fight.
You don't think I'm good enough, Captain?
It was always my dream...
But you don't want me in Amaterasu, do you?
N-No, Sylvia!
I just...
Forget it!
Sylvia!
Why?
Am I that useless, Captain?
But everybody's fighting...
I want to go back to London.
Sylvia...
Let me go!
Wait.
I don't want you to die.
Captain...
Not just you.
I don't want anyone to die.
I couldn't give that order.
I'm a failure as a captain, aren't I?
I always wanted to be a part of Amaterasu.
So I could find my parents,
who went missing in London.
But now I have another goal!
I'm begging you!
Let me fight with you.
Let me fight for you!
Let me be in Amaterasu!
Sylvia...
This room is so cute!
It's supposedly a lab...
Listen, Sylvia.
Y-Yes?
I'm about to install this core into you.
The way this core works, uh...
I have to be the one to do it.
I don't mind if it's you, Captain...
No, I want you to do it!
Oh, then... um...
Well?
Do I look weird?
You're pretty.
I'm glad.
Good work, Sylvia.
Captain...
I love you.
I guess she still needs tuning
before she can sortie.
I won't let anyone die.
I'll save them all.
And for that...
Mom!
I'll bring you back!
The mission starts tomorrow.
Hurry!
Everyone, the Engineering Division
comes bearing gifts!
Wow!
Anti-Magitech particle rifles
and the new railguns!
Anti-material rifles!
My Luger-chan, too!
Luger-chan?
That's its name!
Isn't it cute?
Well, this is enough to make sure
we succeed tomorrow, right?
We can't let Amaterasu outshine us!
Show them what the Masters can do!
Yes, ma'am!
By the way, where is everyone in Amaterasu?
I figured you'd be here.
I like looking at the sea.
And being alone when I do it.
It's fine. You don't have to say anything.
It would make me happy
if you just left, though.
U-Um...
Are you worried about me?
If you are, I'm fine now.
But because of, uh,
how things went last time,
you haven't done your Heart Hybrid yet.
I just said I'm fine.
Are you so stupid that you can't
understand something that simple?
Aine...
Sheesh...
That wasn't like me.
Going crying to an Eros Overlord like you
just because I had a weird dream.
It's the biggest mistake of my life!
The worst moment of my life, too.
What?
I was just worried about you...
I'm me.
No one but Aine Chidorigafuchi.
Right?
I'm looking forward to tomorrow.
As the best pilot in the universe,
I can't wait.
Aine...
Self-Study!!
On account of
Operation Take Back Tokyo
Take Back Tokyo
Tokyo, huh?
Ah, how I've missed my beloved hometown...
...is probably not what you're thinking, huh?
That's right.
When I heard we were going back to Tokyo,
to be honest, I was scared.
I was scared that my past
might crush me again.
But now I can look forward to the future.
It's thanks to Kizuna-kun.
That's right.
Me, too.
I was able to change because of Kizuna.
I realized that it's okay
to rely more on others.
But it's a little upsetting...
...that a single boy like him
was enough to change me.
It's not just that something's changed.
It feels like something new has begun.
Something new has begun, huh?
Is something beginning for her, too?
This is where it all began, right?
Hey, what's wrong?
Why are you crying?
I don't know...
You don't know the reason yourself?
I don't know anything about myself...
H-Hey...
Then I'll think with you.
If you don't know, then I'll
think with you and figure it out.
So...
That's right.
No matter how stubborn and
strong-willed she can be,
she's a crybaby,
and a normal girl like any other.
Back then...
If I'd grabbed her hand,
what would've happened?
Well? You sleep last night?
Yup. Don't worry.
I slept great.
Hi, Kizuna!
Kizuna-kun.
Aine, I'll make sure you're...
Let's go!
Magitech weapons, codename Vikings,
have landed on Ataraxia!
They got here first?
They're here, too!
Fire! Fire!
Leave this to us!
You get to Tokyo!
Scarlet!
Got it!
Let's go!
Eros!
Kuros!
Neros!
Zeros!
Amaterasu has taken off!
Wow! Quite the welcome party!
This was expected!
Everyone split up
and head for the designated points!
Roger!
I can see it!
Fly low and quiet...
Where should I land?
There!
Okay.
Point A setup complete.
About damn time!
Here we go!
It's finally here!
The goddamn data from Point A is here!
Good.
We're getting data from
points B, C, and D, too.
Analyzing data.
Entrance coordinates confirmed.
Launch the second team!
Set the sealing system up immediately
and seal the Entrances!
Roger!
I'm counting on you, everyone!
Now I just have to cause some serious damage!
If you want a decoy operation,
I'll give you one!
What?
What's going on here?
Illustration: Ken Takahashi
We've come back to our homeland
that once was stolen.
There's only one thing for us to do now:
take everything back!
Oh, Hayuru. Don't worry so much
about the complicated stuff.
Next time: Operation Take Back Tokyo -Apocalypse-
Let's just break some things!